<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!-- 
Website Documentation
=======================

## Contents

* Demo category - demo_category_perspectives
* Demo page - demo_page_4pillars

## Notes

* Use noupdate="0" or omit noupdate attribute in data records. Then you can
manage documentation in a git repo and it will update as expected with a
module upgrade.
-->
<odoo>
  <data>
    <record id="demo_category_perspectives" model="document.page">
      <field name="name">Waite Perspectives</field>
      <field name="type">category</field>
      <field name="sequence">1</field>
    </record>


    <record id="demo_page_4pillars" model="document.page">
      <field name="name">Odoo - 4 Pillars of Agility</field>
      <field name="parent_id" ref="demo_category_perspectives"/>
      <field name="content">
        <![CDATA[
        <style>
        :root {
          font-family: monospace;
          }
          h1 {
            text-align: center;
            }
        </style>
        <br>
        <br>
            <h1>Odoo - 4 Pillars of Agility</h1>
            <p>
              As a business is dynamic and processes are constantly changing, so should the systems used to
              manage the business. Odoo is highly flexible, but has its challenges with agility. The best
              Odoo integrators will be experts in key areas dubbed the "4 Pillars of Agility".
              </p>

              <ul>
                <li>
                  <h3>Testing</h3>
                  <p>Testing is the backbone of any change or new development in an Odoo system. The ability
                    of the integrator to efficiently create and maintain tests is a key indicator of success.
                    This includes all forms of testing: unit testing, integration testing, performance testing ...
                  </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                  <h3>Migrations</h3>
                  <p>
                    Migrations are the implementation of a change to the system environment. The primary
                    challenge in Odoo is migrating the database schema, but any change can cause ripple effects
                    up and down the system. The best integrators will have reliable and efficient processes to
                    confidently implement migrations.
                  </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                  <h3>Data Quality Assurance</h3>
                  <p>
                    Data Quality Assurance is important for the business for monitoring KPI's and making confident decisions,
                    but is also critical for the integrator for testing and making
                    system changes. The best integrators will devise monitoring systems and audit procedures
                    to identify irregularities in data and quickly act to resolve any issues.
                  </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                  <h3>Documentation</h3>
                  <p>
                    Documentation is critical to ensure a deep understanding of the business system and the
                    processes it manages. The best integrators will maintain documentation that reflects the
                    most current state of the system and provide it to the business customer as part of the
                    training process, ideally within the Odoo system itself. Documentation should be version
                    controlled alongside the source code and treated as importantly as data schemas and algorithms.
                  </p>
                </li>
              </ul>
            </p>
        <br>
        <br>
        ]]>
      </field>
    </record>
  </data>
</odoo>
